(Penny:)-Hey, can I ask you a question?
-Sure.
(Penny:)You've had this dart board
since I've known you.
(Penny:)But I've never seen you play.
Oh, we played... once.
(Leonard:)I broke a window.
(Penny:)What window?
(Leonard:)That one over there.
(Sheldon:)Leonard,
where are the Skee-Ball tickets?
(Sheldon:)Skee-Ball tickets?
(Sheldon:)Yeah, from when we went
to the arcade three years ago?
(Sheldon:)I finally decided what prize I want.
(Sheldon:)Hurry up.
(Leonard:)If I still have them,
they're probably in the junk box.
(Penny:)-Ooh, what are you gonna get?
-None of your business.
(Sheldon:)But when you see me wearing
a flower in my lapel later,
(Sheldon:)you are most welcome to sniff it.
-Yup, got 'em, here you go.
-Oh, thank you.
(Sheldon:)Here, get yourself an eraser
for your troubles.
(Leonard:)Oh, I forgot about this.
(Leonard:)My aunt made it for me
when I started college.
(Penny:)Aw, did she hate you?